msgpluslive.net 2011-12-13

# Messenger Plus! - Privacy Policy Statement

This privacy policy is intended for those visiting msgpluslive.net (Messenger Plus!) and its affiliated localised domains such as msgpluslive.fr and msgpluslive.nl. Please note that the software product Messenger Plus! Live has a separate license which is included in the setup file and showed before you install.

**Effective Date: August 18, 2006**

Messenger Plus! is committed to protecting your privacy. Messenger Plus! collects no personal information about who visits the site. Messenger Plus! uses a hit service that records information such as which internet service visitors are using, from what country they are coming from, what browser they are using, and such. Messenger Plus! also keeps track of which scripts and skins from the Scripts Database (www.msgplus.net/Downloads/Scripts) and Skins Database (www.msgplus.net/Downloads/Skins) visitors have downloaded and/or rated. This is done by storing a unique number which can't be connected to any personal data. In no way does Messenger Plus! automatically collect personal information from its visitors such as their name or email address.

### Cookies:

Messenger Plus! uses cookies to store data needed for personal preferences which improve user experience, this data doesn't contain any recognisable private information. Cookies are stored on your own computer, and you are free to deny these cookies or delete them whenever you wish. See the help documentation from you internet browser for help on this procedure.

### Will Messenger Plus! disclose the information it collects from visitors?

Messenger Plus! may eventually disclose the aforementioned GENERAL information about visitors (how many visitors, what countries are they from, etc), information that does NOT identify who you are. We may disclose answers to questions such as: During what time periods do we receive the most visitors, what is the most common browser version of our visitors, what are the most popular internet services our visitors use, etc.

### Submitting Scripts and Skins:

Users can voluntarily submit scripts and skins they have created to Messenger Plus!. Any information you provide when you send a script/skin will be stored and be made accessible to the Messenger Plus! team. Only when your script/skin is accepted will we store the following information publicly online:

  * Script/Skin's title
  * Description
  * Developer's Name (as you have provided us, a nickname is just fine)
  * Version number
  * Screenshot
  * Your website URL, if you have provided any
  * The actual script/skins file you have submitted

Users can request at anytime that we delete or change this information (online and offline) by corresponding with us.

### Using the online log service:

When using the MyPlus! log service, you must comply with this contract, all applicable laws.  
You must not use the service to harm others or the service. For example, you must not use the service to harm, threaten, or harass another person, organization, or Yuna Software. You must not: damage, disable, overburden, or impair the service (or any network connected to the service); resell or redistribute the service or any part of it; use any unauthorized means to modify, reroute, or gain access to the service or attempt to carry out these activities; or use any automated process or service (such as a bot, a spider, periodic caching of information stored by Yuna Software, or metasearching) to access or use the service. You may be able to access third-party websites or services via the service; you acknowledge that we are not responsible for such websites or services or content that may be available there.

### Your MyPlus! account:

Only you may use your service account. You must keep your accounts and passwords confidential and not authorize any third party to access or use the service on your behalf, unless we provide an approved mechanism for that. You must contact us right away if you suspect misuse of your accounts or any security breach in the service.

### Your content:

Except for material that we license to you, we don't claim ownership of the content you provide on the service. Your content remains your content. We also don't control, verify, or endorse the content that you and others make available on the service.

You control who may access your content. If you share content in public areas of the service or in shared areas available to others you've chosen, then you agree that anyone you've shared content with may use that content. When you give others access to your content on the service, you grant them free, nonexclusive permission to use, reproduce, distribute, display, transmit, and communicate to the public the content solely in connection with the service and other products and services made available by Yuna Software. If you don't want others to have those rights, don't use the service to share your content.

You understand that Yuna Software may need, and you hereby grant Yuna Software the right, to use, modify, adapt, reproduce, distribute, and display content posted on the service solely to the extent necessary to provide the service.

Please respect the rights of artists, inventors, and creators. Content may be protected by copyright. People appearing in content may have a right to control the use of their image. If you share content on the service in a way that infringes others' copyrights, other intellectual property rights, or privacy rights, you're breaching this contract. You represent and warrant that you have all the rights necessary for you to grant the rights in this section and the use of the content doesn't violate any law. We won't pay you for your content. We may refuse to publish your content for any or no reason. We may remove your content from the service at any time if you breach this contract or if we cancel or suspend the service.

You're responsible for backing up the data that you store on the service. If your service is suspended or cancelled, we may permanently delete your data from our servers. We have no obligation to return data to you after the service is suspended or cancelled. If data is stored with an expiration date, we may also delete the data as of that date. Data that is deleted may be irretrievable.

### Privacy:

In order to operate and provide the service, we collect certain information about you. As part of the service, we may also automatically upload information about your computer, your use of the service, and service performance. In particular, we may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Yuna Software or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the service; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of Yuna Software employees, customers, or the public.

### NO WARRANTY:

We provide the service "as is," "with all faults," and "as available." We don't guarantee the accuracy or timeliness of information available from the service. You acknowledge that computer and telecommunications systems are not fault-free and occasional periods of downtime occur. We do not guarantee the service will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free, or that data loss will not occur. We and our affiliates, resellers, distributors, and vendors give no express warranties, guarantees, or conditions. We exclude any implied warranties, including for merchantability, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, workmanlike effort, and non-infringement. You may have certain rights under your local law. Nothing in this contract is intended to affect those rights, if they are applicable.

### Third Parties:

Messenger Plus! works with third parties that serves ads to this site and provide additional services. They may include:

  * Google Adsense - <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

You can review the privacy policy from each of these services at the addresses provided above.

### Links:

This web site may contain links to other sites. This statement is for the sole use and purpose of Messenger Plus!. Please be aware that Messenger Plus! is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy practices of each and every web site before using the services provided.

### Security:

Messenger Plus! takes every reasonable precaution to protect its users' information. Messenger Plus! has put security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alterations of the information under its control.

### Questions:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.

Messenger Plus! reserves the right to change this policy from time to time. Revised policies will only apply to information collected after the date the policy is changed.
